let MCQS = [{
            question: "To compute Bernoulli numbers, she devised an algorithm for the Analytical Engine.",
    choice1: "Ada Lovelace",
    choice2: "Grace Murray",
    choice3: "Alick Glennie",
    choice4: "Adele Goldberg",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "A computer programming language for scientific, mathematical, and statistical purposes, was designed by John Backus in 1957.",
    choice1: "LISP",
    choice2: "FORTRAN",
    choice3: "CSS",
    choice4: "C Language",
    answer: 1
},
            {
            question: "They must contain an opening and closing tag, and the content.",
    choice1: "HTML ELEMENTS",
    choice2: "HTML TECHNIQUES",
    choice3: "<html>",
    choice4: "<tags>",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "It is a piece of filming equipment to which you can attach your camera, and it aids in the filming process.",
    choice1: "Selfie Stick",
    choice2: "Table",
    choice3: "Peg Bar",
    choice4: "Camera Rig",
    answer: 3
},
            {
            question: "The process after all the drawings are cleaned up, they are then photographed on an animation camera; usually on black and white stock.",
    choice1: "Layouting",
    choice2: "Designing",
    choice3: "Pencil testing",
    choice4: "Animating",
    answer: 2
},
            {
            question: "An animation technique that takes live-action footage and traces it with special tools, similar to how traditional animation styles trace photographs onto glass panels.",
    choice1: "Live Action",
    choice2: "Rotoscoping",
    choice3: "2D Animation",
    choice4: "3D Animation",
    answer: 1
},
            {
               question: "This panel in Photoshop shows you a history of all the changes you have made to your graphic.",
    choice1: "Layers Panel",
    choice2: "Menu Bar",
    choice3: "History panel",
    choice4: "Info panel",
    answer: 2
},{
               question: "This is the place where you'll access different commands to use in Photoshop.",
    choice1: "Layers Panel",
    choice2: "Menu Bar",
    choice3: "History panel",
    choice4: "Info panel",
    answer: 1
},
            {
               question: "This tool lets you make a freeform selection outline around an item.",
    choice1: "Marquee Tool",
    choice2: "Lasso tool",
    choice3: "Crop Tool",
    choice4: "Quick Selection Tool",
    answer: 1
},
            {
               question: "It makes it simple to choose an object by painting over it with a brush.",
    choice1: "Marquee Tool",
    choice2: "Lasso tool",
    choice3: "Crop Tool",
    choice4: "Quick Selection Tool",
    answer: 3
}];